<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:orientation="vertical"
    android:layout_width="wrap_content" 
    android:layout_height="fill_parent"
    android:paddingLeft="0dip"
    android:paddingRight="0dip">
    
	<TextView
		android:layout_width="fill_parent" 
		android:layout_height="fill_parent"
		android:textStyle="bold" 
		android:textColor="#ffffffff"
		android:textSize="32dip"
		android:text="About / Tutorial" 
		android:gravity="center"
		android:layout_gravity="center_vertical" />	    
	
	<View android:layout_width="wrap_content" 
		android:layout_height="4dip" 
		android:background="?android:attr/listDivider"/>
		
		<ScrollView
				android:layout_width="wrap_content" 
		android:layout_height="wrap_content"
		>
		
		<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
	    android:orientation="vertical"
	    android:layout_width="wrap_content" 
	    android:layout_height="fill_parent"
	    android:paddingLeft="0dip"
	    android:paddingRight="0dip">

	<TextView
		android:layout_width="wrap_content" 
		android:layout_height="fill_parent"
		android:textColor="#ffffffff"
		android:textSize="18dip"
		android:text="Welcome to aDose!\n\nAbout aDose:\n\n\taDose is a Sound and Light Machine. Using specific sequences of strobing patters of light and binaural frequences, aDose causes brainwave synchronization. By synchronizing brainwaves to specific rhythms, a user's mood can be significantly altered. Alpha patterns (8-12Hz) cause relaxation, beta (13-30Hz) causes creativity and arounsal, theta (3.5-7.5Hz) causes dreamlike thinking and delta patterns (sub 3.5Hz) cause a sensation similar to deep sleep. (If you\'re interested in the science of this, you should check out the Wikipedia article on Audio-Visual Entrainment).\n\nTutorial\n\n\tTo use aDose, you will need a pair of headphones, a dark room and a comfy place to sit or lay down. Choose your sequence, then hold your phone directly up to your eyes and relax yourself. When you are ready, press begin and let the experience begin. Sequences typically last between ten and twenty minutes. When you are finished, be careful standing up as you may feel quite lightheaded!\n\nSequences:\n\n\tThe different sequences provided create different effects. The meditation sequence is great for focused relaxation, the sleep sequence and REM sequence are nice before bed, the focus and relaxation sequences are great when work is boring or stressful and the creativity and psychadelic sequences are great for mental stimulation. The sequences are produced by different brainwave artists.\n\n If you are interested in becoming a brainwave artist yourself, send us an email as this is a feature we would like to have in upcoming versions of aDose.\n\nCredits:\n\n\taDose is written by New Freedom Applications and is based on the work of Mitch Altman's Brain Machine. The Mediation Sequence is licensed Creative Commons Attribution Share-Alike. New Freedom Applications can be contacted at miserlou@gmail.com\n"
		android:layout_gravity="center_vertical"
		android:padding="12dip" />	
		
    <Button
	    android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceMedium"
        android:id="@+id/resume"
        android:text="Return!!"
      	android:layout_gravity="center"
	    android:layout_width="wrap_content" 
		android:layout_height="90dip"
		android:padding="20dip"
		android:textColor="#000000"
		android:background="@drawable/button"
		android:shadowColor="#ffffff"
		android:shadowDy="-1"
		android:shadowRadius="1"
		android:singleLine="true"
		android:ellipsize="none" />
		
		    <TextView  
	    android:id="@+id/loadingtext"
	    android:layout_width="fill_parent" 
	    android:layout_height="wrap_content"
	    android:textAppearance="?android:attr/textAppearanceSmall"
	    android:text="Please don't use this if you are prone to epileptic seizures."
	    android:textColor="#ffffff"
	    android:padding="7dip"
        android:gravity="center"
    	android:visibility="visible"
    	
    />
    
    </LinearLayout>
    </ScrollView>
   
	<View android:layout_width="fill_parent" 
		android:layout_height="4dp" 
		android:background="?android:attr/listDivider"/>   
       
</LinearLayout>
